她说的笑话我必须得笑  她可是我老板
I have to laugh at her jokes. She's my boss.
那也不用老盯着她胸部吧
Do you have to stare at her boobs, too?
哪有  是她那有块污渍
I wasn't. She had a stain.
你还在回想那形状
And you were trying  to memorize the shape?
什么  我没有  我发誓
What? No. I swear.
我要是说谎  天理难容
If I'm lying, my god strike me down--
我是想  我只是  我也不知道
Yeah, I want to.  I just--I don't know.
是的
Yes. Um..
我不能告诉他  他会抓狂的
I can't tell him, he will freak.
肯定会
He will.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
-谁会抓狂  -什么
- Who'll freak? - What?
你说谁会抓狂
Who's gonna freak?
学校里的人  你不认识的
Oh, um, someone from school. You don't know them.
你确定
Are you sure?
我还以为你的朋友我都认识呢
But I thought I knew  all your friends.
抱歉  老爸  我还有一堆家庭作业
Hey, I'm sorry, dad, but I have a ton of schoolwork.
当然  我明白
Oh, no. Yeah.
什么事都可以跟我谈的  对吧
You know you could  tell me anything, right?
我知道
Yep.
卡塞尔
Castle.
有尸体从天而降
A body falls out of the sky,
难不成是我的错
And somehow that's my fault?
你好  卡塞尔
Hey, Castle.
希望没误了你的要事
I hope we didn't take you away  from something important
或什么约会
Or someone.
你会不会有事瞒着自己老爸
Did you ever keep secrets from your dad?
当然
Sure.
哪类事
What kind?
你真想知道
Do you really want to know?
你的秘密吗  当然
About your secrets? Absolutely.
要是我女儿的嘛...
About my daughter's?
我肯定  其实没什么
You know what? I'm sure it's nothing.
阿丽克西斯不会瞒着我什么的
Alexis would never keep  anything serious from me.
我可是个酷老爸
I'm the cool dad.
头儿  你怎么在这里
Sir, what are you  doing here?
死者名叫杰克·巴克利
The victim's Jack Buckley.
杰克·巴克利是谁
Who's Jack Buckley?
助理地方检察官  是个好人
An assistant district attorney. One of the good guys.
巴克利不喜欢潜规则
Buckley hated making deals,
喜欢把坏人绳之以法
Loved putting bad guys behind bars.
他是警察们最喜欢的那种公诉律师
He's the lawyer every cop wanted prosecuting their case.
看来他不是没有进行反击
Well, looks like he didn't  go down without a fight.
对  他的夹克都扯坏了
Yeah, his Jacket was torn.
在屋顶找到他的公文包
We found his briefcase up on the roof
还有他左脚的鞋子
Along with his left shoe.
犯罪现场小组正在全面清查现场
C.S.U. is doing a full sweep.
杰克块头很大  凶手肯定很强壮
Well, Jack's a big boy. Whoever did it must be strong.
等等  我明白了
Wait. I know what this is.
律师让犯人入狱  犯人觉得蒙冤了
Lawyer puts criminal in jail. Criminal feels wronged.
就杀害了律师  整个一出《海角惊魂》
Criminal kills lawyer.  This is "Cape Fear."
知道他去上面干什么吗
Any idea what he was doing up there?
不  找他的秘书谈过
No, I talked to his secretary,
她说巴克利大约8点左右下班
And she said Buckley left work around 8:00,
直接往西区去了  他家就在那
Heading straight home, which is on the west side.
还有  巴克利乘的是地铁
And get this. Buckley was a subway rider.
他根本没车
He didn't own a car.
那他到东区的停车场是干嘛来了
Then what's he doing at a parking garage  on the east side?
问得好
That's a good question.
巴克利结婚了吗
Was Buckley married?
离异  前妻住在加州
Divorced. Ex-wife lives in California.
查查他前妻那边  先从他私生活查起
Reach out to his wife. Let's start looking
看能找到什么线索
Into his personal life and see what we can find.
市长希望尽快结案
The mayor wants this solved quickly.
杀害执法人员  绝对不能逍遥法外
Nobody kills a law enforcement officer and gets away with it.
真不敢相信他死了
I just can't believe that he's dead.
-你不知道他为何去那个停车场吗  -不
- And you have no idea why he was in the garage? - No.
这是巴克利先生处理的案子的复印件
Here are the printouts of Mr. Buckley's cases you wanted.
谢谢
Thanks.
这出《海角惊魂》里
I'm telling you this "Cape Fear" list
嫌疑人可不少啊
Is gonna be a gold mine of suspects.
看看这个  阿基保尔·斯平克斯
Check out this guy-- Archibald Spinks.
五次谋杀未遂
Five counts of attempted murder,
一次恶意露体
One count of indecent exposure.
你不会以为他想要用那什么杀人吧
You don't suppose he tried to kill 'em with his...
那可不管用
Yeah, that wouldn't work.
巴克利先生收到过恐吓
Had Mr. Buckley ever received any threats,
或者有什么诉讼闹得不愉快吗
Any prosecutions that went ugly?
如果他有段时间没收到恐吓的话
Well, he didn't think he was doing his job right
他就觉得自己工作没做好  但最近没有
If he wasn't being threatened,  but nothing recently, no.
过去几天  他确实有些沮丧
He did seem to be upset  the past few days.
-知道原因吗  -不
- Any idea why? - No.
警察曾带来过个人
You know, there was that man the police brought in.
-什么人  -就在周一午餐之后
- What man? - It was right after lunch on Monday.
警察铐来个凶神恶煞的人
A cop brought in a tough looking guy in handcuffs,
直接带进了巴克利先生的办公室
Took him right in To Mr. Buckley's office
然后在门外等着
And then waited outside.
我们听到门内传来争吵声
Yeah, we heard them yelling through the door,
然后警察就把他带走了
And then the officer took him away.
-这种事经常发生吗  -从未有过
- That kinda thing happen a lot? - Never.
记得那位警察的名字吗
Do you remember the officer's name?
记得  弗兰克  弗兰克·柯蒂斯
Yeah. Frank. Uh, Frank-- Frank Curtis.
柯蒂斯说他不记得
Curtis doesn't remember
为什么巴克利要见那人
Why Buckley asked him to bring the guy in,
但他记得那人的名字  约翰·诺克斯
But he does remember his name. John Knox.
十几项前科  同事正带他过来
Dozens of priors. Uniforms are bringing him in.
我猜这家伙可不是个善茬
I'm guessing this guy isn't exactly an altar boy.
你猜  来吧  我们走
You think? Come on. Let's go.
你的前科很精彩嘛  诺克斯先生
You've got quite a record, Mr. Knox.
你父母肯定以你为荣
Your parents must be proud.
是啊  他们把我的入狱照都贴冰箱上呢
Yeah, they hang all my  mug shots on the fridge.
有话能直说吗
Can we cut to the chase?
两天前  你和巴克利在他办公室发生争执
Two days ago, you had an argument with Buckley in his office.
昨晚  我们发现他被害了
Last night we found him dead.
我想你明白我们的意思
So you can understand our interest.
当然  但你们这是浪费时间
Sure, but you're wasting your time.
-我可没杀那人  -真的吗
- I didn't kill the guy. - Really?
你的记录上可清清楚楚写着了
Because it says here that you have quite a history
好几次试图谋杀  过去两年三次谋杀未遂
Of trying to kill people-- three in the last two years,
没准我还少算了
Or am I missing any?
我可从没被定过罪
I was never convicted of anything.
这可不算是否认
That's not exactly a denial.
你常锻炼吗
Do you work out?
仰卧推举  硬举之类的
You know, bench press, dead lift?
要把个人从屋顶扔下
It must take a lot of upper body strength
对上肢力量要求可不低
To throw a guy off a roof.
这人是谁
Who is this guy?
你跟巴克利为何争执
What did you and Buckley fight about?
那是因为他想控告我人身攻击
Look, he had it out for me because he put me on trial
把我送进监狱  我从未做过  他也确实败诉了
For an assault I didn't commit and he lost.
他不能像条汉子那么勇敢接受
And rather than being a man about it,
反而觉得吓唬我
He decided to rattle my cage,
能证明他是个真正的男子汉
To show me who was the alpha male.
真是有够烦人  还很幼稚
So, yeah, it was annoying and childish,
绝不至于杀人  何况他还是检察官
But not something you kill a guy over, especially a D.A.
我或许是犯了事  但我可不蠢
Now I may be a criminal,  but I'm not...stupid.
巴克利凶案发生时  你有不在场证明吗
Do you have an alibi for Buckley's murder?
我不知道  他什么时候被害的
I don't know. What time was he killed?
-晚上九点半  -在瘾君子匿名互诫会
- 9:30 p.m. - I was at an A.A. meeting.
匿名的  真有意思
Anonymous? That's cute.
你们不相信我
You don't believe me?
也许你们会信我的担保人
Well, then maybe you'll believe my sponsor...
丹尼尔·米勒牧师
Reverend Daniel Miller.
你刚说牧师
Did you say "reverend"?
诺克斯那边查得如何
So where are we with Knox?
不在场证明没疑点
The alibi looks solid.
卡塞尔和贝克特
Castle and Beckett are interviewing
-正找那牧师谈话呢  -法医那边如何
- The good reverend right now. - What about forensics?
没进展  不过我有所发现
Looks like a bust, but I did  find something interesting.
查了巴克利的地铁卡刷卡记录
When checked into Buckley's metro card history.
整个月他每天只刷两次卡
His card only made two swipes a day for the whole month--
早上六点在他公寓附近地铁站刷卡
6:00 a.m. At the subway by his apartment,
晚上八点在他办公室这
8:00 p.m. By his office.
巴克利的生活只剩工作  尤其是离婚之后
Buckley lived for the job, especially after the divorce.
也许是想借工作来逃避烦恼吧
Probably trying to lose himself in the work.
他被害那天  行为异常
On the day he was killed, Buckley did something unusual.
他去了西区77大街
He made an extra trip up to west 77th street
然后才去上班
Before he went to work.
他秘书不知道原因
His secretary has no idea why.
看看我们能否有发现
See if you can find out.
队长  看来有人在跟踪巴克利
Yo, cap. Looks like somebody was following our boy Buckley.
他公寓的门卫说  有这么个人
The doorman in his apartment said that a guy
两天前过来想找巴克利谈谈
Came in there two days ago demanding to talk to Buckley,
不接受拒绝  一定要见
Wouldn't take no for an answer.
门卫几乎是把他丢出去的
Doorman practically had to throw the guy out.
就在巴克利被害当天早上
Then on the morning of Buckley's murder,
门卫发誓说  又见到了那家伙
The doorman swears that he saw the same guy
在那幢大楼外出现
Hanging around outside the building.
我从安保录像中截取了张照片
I snagged a photo off the video surveillance.
先从罪犯照片里开始查
Start looking through  some mug shot books.
谢谢您  牧师
Thank you, reverend.
-很高兴见到您  -谢谢
- Pleasure meeting you. - Thanks.
是关于案子的
Is this for our case?
是  这人试图闯入巴克利的公寓
Yeah, the guy who tried to hassle Buckley at his building.
等等  我认识这人
Wait a second. I know this guy.
没错  在我的“海角惊魂”名单里
Yes. My "Cape Fear" file.
就在这里  就在...这里
Right here. Right... Here.
他叫诺曼·杰赛普
His name is Norman Jessup.
四年前  巴克利负责
Buckley got him four years ago
他的银行劫案  有保安中枪
On a bank robbery where a guard got shot.
看到没  我说过我的档案能破这案子
See? I told you this file would solve this case.
记录上说他两周前出狱了
It says here he got out two weeks ago
法院受理了他的上诉
When his conviction was overturned
并且为他翻案了
By the appellate court on a technicality.
听上去杰赛普只该庆祝
That sounds like a reason for Jessup
而不是去杀了巴克利
To celebrate not to kill Buckley.
除非巴克利已经准备好再次上诉
Yeah, except Buckley already filed an intent to retry.
他胜诉的话  杰赛普将再次入狱两年
Jessup was looking at another two years in jail if Buckley won.
这倒可能会让杰赛普抓狂
Well, that might have  made Jessup a little mad.
没错  然后就是
Right, and then it's all...
你给我出来  出来  不管你躲在哪
"Come out, come out wherever you are."
就这样  你心目中的狄尼洛[出演教父二]
Really? That's your De Niro?
查查他现在的住址  列份相关人员清单
Get a current address and a list of known associates.
我想看看杰赛普怎么说
I'd like to hear what Jessup has to say.
等等  你全搞错了
Wait. Wait. You got it all wrong.
得了  警察  散开
Hey! Come on! Police! Break it up!
你不打算做点什么
Are you gonna do something?
在酒吧劝架  肯定会遭殃
Breaking up a bar fight is a sure way to get hit.
别担心  马上就好
Don't worry. It'll be over in a minute.
我也在酒吧打过架
You know, I was in a bar fight once.
真的  谁赢了
Really? Who won?
让我猜猜
Ow! Ah! Oh, let me guess.
肯定不是你
Not you.
杰赛普先生  想找茬吗
You want to fight, Mr. Jessup?
先想办法搞定你的谋杀指控吧
You can fight a murder charge.
抱歉  伙计
Yo, I'm sorry, man.
我不是有意
I didn't mean to embarrass you
让你在女友面前难堪的
In front of your girlfriend there.
我可不是他女友  我是凶案组的探长
I am not his girlfriend. I am a homicide detective.
还有  你该更把这当回事
And you should be taking this a little bit more seriously.
酒吧的那人  是他挑起的  好吗
Hey, that guy in that bar, he started this whole thing, okay?
他以为我是在勾搭他女友
He thought I was hitting on his girlfriend,
我可没有勾搭他女友
And I was not hitting on his girlfriend.
真是个天大的误会
It was just a big misunderstanding.
对  就像那起银行劫案一样
Right. Just like the bank robbery.
正是  我根本不知道
Exactly. I had no idea my buddies
我朋友打算抢劫那银行  一点都不知道
Were gonna rob that bank--  no idea at all.
他们说自己车坏了  要我载他们一程
They said their car broke down and they needed a ride.
我就让他们搭车了
And I gave them a ride.
这种说话没让巴克利采信
And that argument didn't sway Buckley?
你能信吗
Can you believe it?
他告诉我的律师  那个保安中枪了
He told my lawyer that the guard got shot,
因此  在法律上
And therefore, in the eyes of the law,
我跟枪杀他的那人  一样负有责任
I was just as responsible as the guy who shot him.
那肯定让你十分恼火
That must have made you angry.
你怎么看巴克利
How'd you feel about the fact that Buckley
打算上诉你的案子  并让你服完
Was gonna retry your case and try to make you serve
最后两年刑
The final two years of your sentence?
说真的吗  探长  我会哭得像个婴儿
Honestly, lady? I cried like a baby.
蹲监狱不好受  我不想回去
Prison is not fun, okay? I did not want to go back.
我想如果能和巴克利先生谈谈
I figured if I could just talk to Mr. Buckley,
就可以告诉他我从哪儿来的
I could let him know where I'm coming from.
所以你去了巴克利的公寓
Which is what you were doing at Buckley's building.
慢着慢着  我是跟着他几天了
Whoa. Whoa. I followed the man around for a few days, okay?
只为等自己有勇气去和他谈
Just so I could get my courage up to talk to him.
你跟踪巴克利
You were stalking Buckley?
跟踪是一个非常难听的词
Stalking is a pretty damn ugly word.
不要说是跟踪  好吗
Let's not use stalking, okay?
我只是想弄清他的底细
I was just trying to feel the guy out.
明白我的意思吗  试着说服他
You know what I mean? Trying to convince him, you know?
以防你们没注意到
In case you guys haven't noticed,
我是个比较擅长运用文字的人
I'm somewhat of a wordsmith, you know?
一个真正的大师  精通于
A real master of, you know, of, uh...
文字
Words?
昨晚九点到十点你在哪里
Where were you between 9:00  and 10:00 last night?
就坐在你们刚抓我的酒吧
I was sitting in the bar you guys just dragged me out of.
好了  我们会进一步调查你得证词
Okay. Well, we're gonna check into your alibi.
在这期间  你会继续被监禁
In the meantime, you're going back into holding
直到我们有空处理打架的事
Until we can process you for assault.
怎么这样  我说了我很抱歉
Oh, oh, come on! I said I was sorry.
等等  巴克利的神秘之旅
Wait. Buckley's mystery trip.
昨天早上  你跟着巴克利去住宅区了吗
Were you following Buckley uptown yesterday morning?
是的  我跟着他
Yeah, yeah, I was.
-他去哪儿了  -他在某栋豪华大楼外
- Where did he go? - He met some Asian dude
见了一个亚洲人
Outside this real fancy apartment building.
然后他们就吵起来了
Then they started to argue with each other
你们认为可能是那个人杀了他
You think maybe that's the guy who killed him?
如果再看到那栋楼  能认出来吗
Would you recognize the building if you saw it again?
当然  那边我很熟
Oh, yeah. I get around.
去一趟吧
Road trip.
你们介意我把这玩意取下来吗
Hey, you guys mind if I take these things off?
我感觉很老套
I'm starting to feel like a stereotype
坐在警车后面兜风  还戴着这玩意儿
Riding around in the back of a police car wearing 'em.
可以  需要钥匙吗
Sure. Do you want my key?
免了  我会弄  谢谢
No. I got it. Thanks.
你怎么弄开的
How did you do that?
我很会开锁
I've always been good with locks.
当我还在牢里的时候  我就想
When I was in the joint, I was thinking,
我怎样才能利用这个  并从中获利呢
How can I take this and make it more productive, you know?
所以我就申请了锁匠学校
So I been applying to locksmith schools.
但  你知道  他们不接收我
But, you know, they won't let me in
就因为我是犯人  能相信吗
On account that I'm a felon. Can you believe that?
一个犯人想当锁匠
A felon who wants to be a locksmith.
没法不令人怀疑
What could possibly go wrong there?
可以别想得这么卑鄙吗
You don't have to be mean about it.
如果想当锁匠的话  就听好了
If you're gonna be a locksmith, you gotta listen.
左手到右边  右手在上面
Left to right, right over left.
我觉得我越弄越紧了
I think I made it tighter.
杰赛普  看到那楼了吗
Jessup, do you see the building?
-还没  -现在转过来
- Uh, that's a negative. - Now bring it around...
你好  阿拉克西斯  找你爸吗
Oh, hey. Alexis. Uh, are you looking for your dad?
找我  好  什么事
To me? Okay, what's up?
行  那七点半在萨顿酒店见
Yeah, yeah. We can meet at Sutton's around 7:30.
可以吗
Is that okay?
好的  到时候见
All right, I'll see you then.
是阿拉克西斯吗  什么事
Was that Alexis calling you? Why?
她需要我给她出主意
She needed my advice.
关于什么
About what?
不知道  可能不是什么大事
I don't know. It's probably no big deal.
当你对你父亲隐瞒小秘密的时候
When you kept secrets from your father,
那不是什么大事吗
Was it not a big deal?
知道吗  我不会问的
You know, I'm not even gonna ask.
就是右手边的那楼
That's the building on the right-hand side.
-就是那儿  -好的
- Right there. - Okay.
我们去抓住他们
Let's go get 'em.
不包括你  是我们
Not you. Us.
801号公寓  好的  谢谢
Apartment 801? Okay. Thanks.
原来
So it turns out
这栋楼里唯一的亚裔房客是保罗·周
That the building's only Asian tenant is Paul Chou,
而他正是巴克利前妻的哥哥
Who just happens to be Buckley's ex-brother-in-law.
那可能不是《海角惊魂》了
Oh, well, maybe it's not "Cape Fear" then.
而可能是《家仇》
Maybe it's "Family Feud."
可能离婚让巴克利很同甘苦
Maybe Buckley's bitter divorce
带来了很多不愉快  从而引起了打斗
Caused enough hard feelings that things turned violent?
我不明白  我已经几个月没见杰克了
I don't understand. I haven't seen Jack in months
自从他和我妹妹离婚之后就没见过了
Not since he divorced my sister.
是吗
Really?
可惜我有目击证人
Because I have an eyewitness
昨天早上他看到你们争吵
Who saw the two of you arguing yesterday morning.
那也就意味着你对我说谎
So that means you're lying to me.
她讨厌别人说谎
She hates being lied to.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
那好  我们到警察局去
Great. Let's go down to the precinct.
我会安排你戴手铐走一趟
I'll arrange a perp walk,
你可以尽情表演给那些记者们看
And you can put on a show for the cameras.
享受你的嫌犯之旅
Love a good perp walk.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
前天晚上
The night before last,
我被个戴滑雪面具的人袭击了
I was attacked by a man in a ski mask.
他警告我  让我叫巴克利远离丹东
He warned me to tell Buckley to back off Danton
-否则他就毁了我  -谁是丹东
- Or he would ruin me. - Who's Danton?
我不知道  但杰克肯定知道
I don't know, but Jack definitely knew him.
他说他不会轻易放过自己的
He said he wasn't gonna let him get away with this.
那就是我们吵架的原因
That's why we were fighting.
我告诉杰克至少听一次劝
I told Jack to listen for once in his life.
-他得保护我  -为什么
- He had to protect me.  - From what?
-那不关你的事  -但嫌犯之旅是
- That's none of your business. - Perp walk it is.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
我有
I have a...
对女孩
Slight fondness...
略微有些偏爱
For girls.
年轻女孩
Young girls?
胖女孩
Fat girls?
学生妹
Schoolgirls?
应召女郎
Call girls.
还有别人知道你这爱好吗
Oh. Who else knows about this fondness?
只有那些女孩们
Just the girls.
事实上  女孩们  还有拉皮条的
Actually, the girls...and their pimp.
可能就是那个叫丹东的
Whose name is probably Danton.
好吧  没错  但我没有撒谎
O-okay, fine. But I wasn't really lying.
我从没见过丹东
I-I've actually never met Danton.
我从一个朋友那里拿到的电话
Uh, I got the phone number for the agency from a friend.
我打了电话  他们派个女孩来
I call it, and then send over a girl.
那么巴克利在调查丹东的应召生意
So Buckley is investigating Danton's call girl ring.
当丹东发现
When Danton discovers
巴克利的大舅子是个客户
That Buckley's brother-in-law is a client,
他发出警告  别管闲事否则伤害他家人
He sends a message--back off or your family gets hurt.
然后巴克利没有退步  丹东就杀了他
And then when Buckley doesn't back down, Danton kills him.
那我们怎样找到丹东呢
So how do we find Danton?
找个应召女郎来问问
We talk to one of the call girls.
打那个电话  让他们派个女孩来
Call that number and tell him to bring one of his girls over.
告诉她穿性感一点
And tell her to wear something sexy.
我们理所当然该享受这次询问的
No reason we can't enjoy this interview.
保罗  等不及要见我了
Hey, Paul. Couldn't wait to see me, huh?
事实上  是我要见你
Actually, I'm the one who asked for the date.
这不是巴克利办公室的女孩吗
Isn't that the girl from Buckley's office?
她之前看起来是这样吗
Did she look like that before?
一个应召女郎怎么又
So how exactly does a call girl
为超级检察官杰克·巴克利工作
End up working for Jack Buckley, super D.A.?
我被逮捕了吗
Am I under arrest?
如果你不好好回答问题的话  就逮捕你
You will be if you don't answer the question.
杰克曾是我的客人
Jack was a client.
抱歉  斯嘉丽  我不相信这一点
I-I'm sorry, Scarlett. I don't believe that.
大概一年前我就开始见他了
I started seeing him about a year ago.
自他离婚就从未和任何人在一起
He hadn't been with anyone since his divorce.
他很孤独  你明白吗
He was just lonely, you know?
我们在一起的时候  大多是在聊天
We'd spend most of his dates talking.
他带我到高级餐厅
He'd take me to fancy restaurants...
尽管我告诉他没必要这样
Even though I told him he didn't have to.
但我觉得他是想尽量弄得
But I think he wanted to make it feel
正常一点
As normal as possible.
然后有一天  他看见
Then one night, he saw...
我包里有本法律书
A law book in my bag.
我告诉他我做这行
I told him I was only working as an escort
是为了供自己读法律学校
To pay my way through law school.
几个月后  他说他的办公室
A few months later, he said he had an internship
需要一个实习生
Opening up in his office.
问我是否感兴趣
Would I be interested?
他想帮你脱离这一行
He wanted to help you escape the life?
丹东是谁
Who's Danton?
-不知道  -别对我们撒谎  斯嘉丽
- I don't know. - Don't lie to us, Scarlett.
我没有
I'm not.
我知道他是管事的  但我从未见过他
I-I know he runs the business, but I've never met him.
我不是站街女
It's not like I'm a streetwalker
而他也没戴着软呢帽  穿长皮大衣
And he's in a fedora and a long fur coat.
他控制整个流程  来掩盖他的身份
He's organized the entire operation to protect his identity.
女孩们都是独立签约
The girls are independent contractors.
客人们按号码来编排
The clients are all given numbers
因此我们不知道他们的姓
So we don't know their last names.
他们用信用卡付费
They pay the business by credit card.
我们的钱直接转到银行卡里
And our fees get deposited directly into our bank accounts.
在女孩们和管理人之间
Creating the perfect firewall
形成完美的防火墙
Between the girls and the management.
因此当我们抓到你们
So then when we arrest you
你们也无法供出丹东
You can't give up Danton.
因为我不知道他是谁
Because I don't know who he is.
我无法相信杰· 巴克利会嫖娼
I can't believe Jack Buckley was seeing prostitutes.
是啊  但是他一天工作14小时
Yeah, well, he worked 14 hours a day,
没有社交生活
Didn't have a social life.
可能他只是需要陪伴
Maybe he just wanted a little easy company.
但事情还是有点疑问
Well, the math just doesn't add up, though.
巴克利被警告远离丹东
Buckley was warned to back off Danton.
为什么巴克利会调查
Why would Buckley be investigating
他在享受的应召服务呢
A call girl service he was using?
可能丹东试图敲诈巴克利
Maybe Danton tried to blackmail Buckley
却引火烧身了
And it backfired.
然后丹东就通过恐吓他大舅子
So then Danton tried to scare Buckley
来吓吓他
By threatening his brother-in-law.
然而没起作用  丹东就杀了巴克利
And then when that didn't work, Danton killed Buckley.
没错  先尽全力查找
All right. Let's find out everything we can
丹东是何许人也
About this Danton character.
让莱恩和埃斯波西托明天早上
Have Ryan and Esposito reach out to
查查那家应召公司
Vice in the morning.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
卡塞尔  我需要你签署对杰赛普的控告
Castle, I need you to sign these charges against Jessup
然后我再寄到市区
So I can send him downtown.
怎么
What?
不  别告诉我  你觉得他还不错
No, don't tell me you've got a soft spot for this guy.
他是个文字大师
He's a wordsmith.
好吧  没关系
Okay. Fine.
你好  我是贝克特
Hi, it's Beckett.
终止对杰赛普的控告
Uh, charges are being dropped against Jessup.
放了他吧  好  谢谢
Process him out. All right. Thank you.
希望你们相处愉快
I hope the two of you are very happy together.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
有事  断了一个鞋跟
No. I...broke a heel.
我猜一下  这是你最爱的一双鞋
Let me guess. They were your favorite pair,
家族世代相传
Passed through your family for generations.
我的曾祖母穿过这双鞋坐着"五月花"号
My great-great-grandmother wore them over on the "Mayflower."
我就知道
I knew it.
那像你这么漂亮的女孩怎么
So what's a nice girl like you...
想知道  那是你的底线
Really? That's your line?
我很传统
I'm old-fashioned.
我开着一辆蓝色破甲壳虫来到纽约
I came to New York in this ancient blue beetle.
底板已锈迹斑斑
The floor was so rusted,
而且从中间凹陷了
It literally sagged in the middle.
但我仍然记得穿过那座桥
But I can still remember coming over the bridge
看到这座城市就在我眼前
And seeing the city right there in front of me.
我以为一切都会很美好
I thought everything was gonna be perfect.
我有预感这个故事没走向美好
Something tells me this story takes a turn for the worse.
第一天晚上  有人弄开我的车
The first night, uh, somebody broke into my car
偷走了我所有的东西
And stole all my stuff.
然后本该合住的大学朋友
Then the college friend I was gonna stay with
告诉我她男朋友要搬进来了
Told me her boyfriend was moving in.
-我得另找地方  -惨
-  I had to find another place. - Ooh.
但不管怎样  我活下来了
But somehow, I survived.
一整年基本没吃什么  住在衣橱里
Spent a year barely eating, Living in a closet.
当一个朋友提起做这个的时候
When a friend mentioned doing this,
我想  不可能比现在差吧
I thought...couldn't be worse.
是这样吗
And is it?
其实更糟糕
Mostly no.
谢谢你听我说这些
Thanks for listening.
晚安  卡塞尔
Good night, Castle.
-你是去见阿丽克西斯吗  -是啊
- You going to meet Alexis?  - Yeah.
我能去吗
Can I come?
-不能  -但我想去
- No. - But I want to.
你干嘛这么担心  卡塞尔
Why are you so worried, Castle?
你不是个酷老爸吗
I thought you were the cool dad.
我是啊
I am.
是什么秘密
What's the secret?
全在于呼吸  亲爱的
All in the breathing, dear.
不是  我是问阿丽克西斯的秘密是什么
No, what's Alexis' secret
她想告诉贝克特却不愿告诉我
That she'll tell Beckett about but not me?
我不知道  有些事情女人
I don't know. There are some things a woman
只想跟另一个女人讲
Wants to talk to another woman about.
《纽约时报》
The "New York Times"
都称赞我的女主角们很有内涵
Praised the depth of my female characters.
我知道  我非常为你感到骄傲
I know. And I couldn't be prouder.
但这就是现实
But this is real life.
很显然  阿拉克西斯崇拜贝克特
And obviously, Alexis looks up to Beckett.
她聪慧  坚强又独立
And Beckett's smart and strong and independent.
你也是啊
So are you.
你真贴心
That's sweet.
我已经过了40岁了
I'm on the wrong side of 40
-不能体会阿里克西斯的心情  -40
- For what Alexis is going through right now. - Forty?
还是省省吧  孩子
Deflect all you want, kiddo.
但我看到你眼里的恐惧了
But I recognize the fear in your eyes.
你怕阿里克西斯比你想象的更像
You're afraid Alexis has more Rick Castle in her
里克·卡塞尔
Than you thought.
晚上好  宝贝
Hey, sweetie.
你和贝克特谈的怎么样啊
How did your talk with Beckett though?
很好啊  她人真的很不错
Fine. She's really nice.
是啊  她是挺不错的
Yeah, she is.
女儿  如果你不想告诉我
You know, sweetheart, if you don't want to tell me
你和贝克特谈了些什么  你大可不必
What you talked about with Beckett, you don't have to.
好  谢谢爸爸
Ok. Thanks dad.
你到底怎么回事
What is the matter with you?
你为什么不直接问他
Why didn't you just ask her?
那样就显得我很爱管闲事
Because that would be prying,
酷老爸们是不会那样做的
And cool dads don't do that.
他们会背着他们的女儿
They go behind their daughter's back,
去求贝克特告诉他们
And they beg Beckett to tell 'em.
你以前和巴克利一起合作过吗
You ever have any cases with Buckley?
有几次
A few.
如果你问我的话  我们关系有点僵
Guy was wound a little tight if you ask me.
他自视为正义的使者
Saw himself as a crusader for justice.
-埃斯波西托  -吉尔·玛兹扎  你好啊
- Yo, Esposito.  - Gil Mazzara. What's up, man?
-你好啊  -你还在看
- How you doing?  - So you still looking
那些破案意见吗
At dirty pictures of advice？
是啊  让你妈妈再寄些新的过来吧
Yeah, tell your mom to send over some new ones.
我手中的那些过时了
The ones I got are getting old.
-认识我的搭档莱恩吗  -认识
- You know my partner--Ryan?  - Yeah.
牛奶蜂蜜  很高兴见到你
Honey milk. Nice to see you
我听说你在追查丹东
So, uh, I hear you're looking to talk about Danton.
是啊  你认识他
Yeah. You know him?
是  五年前我抓过他
Yeah, I arrested him five years ago.
真名叫丹·托内利
Real name's Dan Tonelli.
丹  东
Dan-ton.
是的  他现在在绿岛监狱
Yeah. He's currently serving
服刑  刑期七年
A 7-year stretch in green haven correctional.
等等  他还在狱中
Wait a minute. He's still in prison?
是巴克利把他弄进去的
And your boy Buckley put him there.
巴克利起诉了丹东
Buckley prosecuted Danton
没错  他全力支持我们 要定他的罪
Yeah. And he was all over us to make a rock-solid case.
我们的证据足可以判他20年了
We gave Buckley enough to put the guy away for 20 years.
托内利在狱中还可能继续操控
Could Tonelli still be running the
这些业务吗
Operation out of prison.
这些应召生意就像是专卖店
These call girl rings are like franchises.
生意会易手  但名字却不变
The business changes hands, but the name stays the same.
那谁是新丹东呢
So who's the new Danton?
我要是知道就好了  他就像个幽灵
I wish I knew. Guy's like a ghost.
每次快要抓到他时  他就消失了
Every time we think we're getting close, he disappears.
去年申请了五张搜查令  每次我们出现
Five warrants in the last year, and every time we show up,
就像知道我们要来  现场都已清理完毕
The place has been cleared out like he knew we were coming.
给监狱打个电话  让他们把托内利带来
You call the prison. Get 'em bring Tonelli over here.
你们看见贝克特了吗
Hey, you guys see Beckett?
她和头一起去市政厅汇报新案情了
She went with the captain to update city hall on the case.
她应该马上就回来了
She'll be here in a minute.
出什么事了吗
Something wrong?
没有  有
No. Yes.
我觉得我女儿在对我隐瞒什么
I think my daughter might be keeping something from me.
-可能她被开出学校了  -什么
- Maybe she got kicked outta school.  - What?
或者她在吸毒
Or she's doing drugs.
青少年怀孕率正在上升
Mm-hmm. Teen pregnancy is on the rise.
行了  你们见过我女儿
Whoa. All right, you've met my daughter.
她已经尽力做到完美了
You know that she is the closest thing to perfect as humanly possible.
卡塞尔  你跟我们做事这么久了
Castle, come on. You've been with us long enough to know
应该知道人常常表里不一
That people are never who you think they are.
很可能你的完美女儿并不是
Isn't it possible your perfect daughter
你想象的那样完美
Isn't as perfect as you think?
丹东到了没
Is Danton here yet?
到了  在一号审讯室
Yep. Interrogation room one.
等等  丹东
Wait, Danton?
走吧  卡塞尔  快跟上
Come on, Castle. Keep up.
我们带你来是想谈谈丹东
We brought you in here to talk about Danton.
陈芝麻烂谷子了
Ancient history.
这上面说  巴克利和你达成了一份
It says here, Buckley made a plea deal with you--
认罪协议  用7年换20年
7 years instead of 20.
但我听说巴克利不涉及潜规则
But I heard Buckley doesn't make deals.
我能说什么呢  只能说我运气好
What could I say? I got lucky.
巴克利同意做交易的唯一原因是
The only reason that Buckley would agree to a deal
你能还他更大的人情
Is because you brought him something big in return.
那是什么呢
So what was it?
-你们为什么不问他  -因为他死了
- Why don't you ask him?  - Because he's dead.
什么  怎么死的
What? How?
两天前他被谋杀了
He was murdered two nights ago.
我们认为
We believe that the same person
你的接班人就是凶手
Who took over your operation's killed him...
有什么好笑的
What's so funny?
那样的话  他得是自杀
Well, you see, that would make it a suicide.
-自杀  -等等
- Suicide?  - Wait a minute.
你是说杰克·巴克利就是新丹东
You're saying that Jack Buckley was the new Danton?
是巴克利跟我做的交易
Buckley made me a deal.
我给他提供客户名单  还有那些小姐们
I provide him with my client list, my girls,
他帮我减13年刑
He knocks 13 years off my sentence.
那肯定无需多想
It was a no-brainer.
我们的检察官拉皮条
Our D.A. was a pimp.
杰克·巴克利就是丹东
Jack Buckley was Danton.
所以所有搜查都没有成果
That's why all vice's warrants failed.
搜查令得经过他手
They had to go through the D.A's office,
巴克利知道他们来了
And Buckley saw them coming.
他处在保护应召公司的最佳位置
He was in the perfect position to protect his operation.
但为什么一个受人尊敬的检察官
But why would a respected prosecutor
会去拉皮条
Become a pimp?
-为了那些装备  -是因为钱
-The outfits.  - It was the money.
巴克利的前妻把他的钱全卷走了
Buckley's ex-wife took him to the cleaners.
要付赡养费  还有自己的账单
Between alimony and his own bills,
巴克利早破产了
Buckley was beyond broke.
我敢打赌肯定不止因为钱
You know what? I'm bettin' it was more than just the money.
每个人都在谈论杰克·巴克利有多厉害
Everybody's talking about how great Jack Buckley was,
他代表的是法律
How he was the law.
一旦你开始那样想
You start thinking like that,
有时候你就会觉得
Sometimes you can start thinking
你自己高于法律
Maybe you are above the law.
以为自己能解决任何事情
That you can get away with anything.
长官  市长是怎样处理这个消息的
Sir, how did the mayor handle the news?
你们不会想知道的
Whew. You don't want to know..
但是  这样讲不通
Okay, this doesn't make any sense.
如果巴克利是新丹东  那为什么蒙面人
If Buckley was the new Danton, then why would the masked man
要告诉巴克利远离丹东
Tell Buckley to back off of Danton?
巴克利不会威胁他自己的
Buckley wouldn't threaten himself.
除非巴克利已经不是老板了
Unless Buckley wasn't the boss anymore.
-恶意的接收  -肯定是
-A hostile takeover.  - Of course.
我们知道丹东只是商业名
We know Danton was just a business name.
那么  远离丹东
So "back off of Danton"
就是新老板在告诉旧老板
Was the new boss telling the old boss,
"不要牵牵绊绊
"Don't resist the takeover
否则就要他声名扫地"
Or I'll start ruining reputations."
理论上讲得通  但怎样证明
Makes sense in theory, but how do you prove?
找个小姐来谈谈
We talk to the call girl.
不可能
There is no way
斯嘉丽不知道巴克利是老板
That Scarlett didn't know that Buckley was in charge.
不  说真的  阿里克西斯昨晚
No, seriously, what did Alexis
到底对你说了些什么
Tell you last night?
我答应她不说出去的
I promised I wouldn't say.
那好  至少告诉我是不是坏事
Well, at least tell me if it was bad.
顺便替你解脱烦恼吗
And put you out of your misery?
-我们想找斯嘉丽  -她在收拾东西
- We're looking for Scarlett.  - She's packing her things.
我们不能让应召女郎在这里工作
We can't have call girls working here.
是啊  只准拉皮条的
No, only pimps.
探长
Detective.
能让我们单独谈谈吗
Could you give us a moment, please?
斯嘉丽  你对我们撒谎了
Scarlett, you lied to us.
巴克利是你们的老板
Buckley was running the call girl ring,
而你不可能不知道
And there's no way that you didn't know.
求你们了  我不得不撒谎
Please. I had to lie.
如果他知道我全招了  他会杀了我
He'd kill me if he thought I told you anything.
谁会杀你  新丹东吗
Who'd kill you, the new Danton?
有人接管了巴克利的生意  那个人是谁
Someone took over Buckley's business. Who was it?
-回答我  -他以前是替巴克利工作的
- Answer me.  - He used to work for Buckley.
他负责保证我们的安全以及
He made sure no one hurt the girls and
-客户付款  -他叫什么名字
- Everyone paid.  - What was his name?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you that.
斯嘉丽  我不想再和你玩下去了
Scarlett, I'm done playing.
你一直在说谎  别以为我不能
You've done nothing but lie to us. Don't think that I'm not
以妨碍司法公正  或我能想到的罪名
Gonna send you away for obstruction of justice
送你进监狱
And anything else that I can think of.
他会杀了我的
He'll kill me.
我们不会让这种事发生的
We won't let that happen.
贝克特探长可以帮助你
Detective Beckett can help you,
但你得先帮助我们
But you have to help us first.
然后我会怎样呢
And then what happens to me?
你以为我就能当律师了吗
You think I'm gonna be a lawyer now?
杰克打算给我写封推荐信
Jack was gonna write me a letter of recommendation,
拉点关系  给我找份工作
Pull some strings to get me a job.
-现在谁会帮我  -老实说  没有人
- Who's gonna help me now?  - Honestly? No one.
你得自己帮助自己  斯嘉丽
You're gonna have to do it by yourself, Scarlett.
不过我相信你可以
And I got a feeling that you can.
告诉我们新老板是谁
Tell us who the new boss is...
贝克特探长可以保证
And detective Beckett will make sure
没有人会知道是你招供的
No one knows it was you who talked to us.
你保证
You promise?
是的
Yes.
他叫约翰·诺克斯
His name is John Knox.
诺克斯  但那是
Knox? But that's--
巴克利抓进来的那个人
The guy that Buckley dragged in here in handcuffs.
一个检察官怎么能和罪犯做生意
How does a prosecutor get into business with a criminal?
拉皮条的在外面混不容易啊
Well, it's hard out there for a pimp...
他又是个检察官
Who's also a D.A.
以他写小说很适合
Ooh, that'd be a good character for a novel.
一个明星检察官
A star prosecutor who's always excelled
做任何事都略胜一筹
At anything he's ever done...
他可能没想到做一个拉皮条的
He couldn't possibly imagine that being a pimp
会超出自己的能力范围
Would be a bigger job than he could handle by himself.
但某一天他接到一个电话
But one day he gets a call--
他的一个小姐被客户给打了
One of his girls has been knocked around by a client.
他意识到对此束手无策
He realizes there's nothing he can do about it.
-他是一个公众人物  -然后呢
- He's a very public figure.  - Mm-hmm.
因此一个白领检察官决定雇用
So a white-collar prosecutor decides to hire
一个蓝领保镖
A blue-collared enforcer.
又不能明目张胆的招人
Can't exactly take out an ad on craigslist for that,
但幸运的是  他有一大票
But fortunately enough, he has a big stack
合格的候选人在手上
Of qualified candidates sitting right on his desk.
他就从中挑选了约翰·诺克斯
Which is where he found John Knox.
他总能有办法避免监禁
A criminal who mostly managed to stay out of prison.
-也让他成为了不起的罪犯  -没错
- Which makes him a smart criminal.  - Yeah.
巴克利提出交易
Buckley offers him a deal--
"来替我工作  我帮你销案"
"Come work for me, I'll throw your case."
诺克斯同意了
And Knox does.
有段时间  大家都高兴
For a while, everyone's happy.
但后来诺克斯决定
But then Knox decides
他不再想当老二了
He's not happy being number two anymore.
他拿了巴克利的客户名单
He takes Buckley's client list,
并让巴克利走人
And let Buckley to take a hike.
他知道巴克利如果不暴露自己
Knowing that Buckley can't do anything about it
-拿他毫无办法  -没错
- Without risking exposure.  - Mm-hmm.
但巴克利一生从未在斗争面前退缩
But Buckley's never backed down from a fight in his life.
他让警察把他抓进来
He gets the cops to drag Knox down to his office
提醒他谁才是老板
To remind him who's boss.
但诺克斯以此为切口
But Knox took it up a notch,
威胁巴克利的大舅子
Sending a warning shot across Buckley's bow
来警告他
By threatening his brother-in-law.
但巴克利不愿意退让
And when Buckley wouldn't back down
诺克斯把他从停车场顶楼扔了下来
Knox threw him off the roof of a parking garage.
天哪  如果我们有证据就好了
Jeez, if only we have some proof.
要什么证据啊  这么精彩的故事
Who needs proof? What a great story.
不过  诺克斯有不在场证据
Of course, Knox has an alibi.
但是  可能你是对的
You know, maybe you're right.
可能诺克斯够聪明  他可以派别人
Maybe Knox is smart. Maybe he sent someone else.
我喜欢情节曲折离奇
Ooh, I like the twist--
保镖也有保镖
The enforcer has an enforcer.
但是是谁呢
But who?
不  这个效果不错  这个很好
No, it worked out well. It was good.
行  我待会再跟你们谈  好吗
You know, I'll talk to you guys later, okay?
你好  还记得我们吗
Hi. Remember us?
我当然记得你
I definitely remember you.
有几个问题想问你
We need to ask you a few questions.
我已经答过了
I already answered your questions.
可能你没看到她的警徽
Maybe you didn't see the badge.
我看到了
Oh, I saw it.
小姐们准备好了吗  棒极了
You ladies ready? Excellent.
祝你们两位玩得愉快
You two have a nice evening.
谁饿了  你们想干什么
Who's hungry? What do you guys feel like?
你不打算拦住他吗
Aren't you gonna stop him?
我不能  除非我们逮捕他
I can't. Unless we arrest him,
根据法律  他没义务跟我们谈话
The law says that he doesn't have to talk to us,
-他明白这一点  -那就逮捕他啊
- And he knows that.  - So arrest him.
凭什么呢
On what grounds?
我们向斯嘉丽保证过  不把她扯进来
We promised Scarlett that we'd keep her out of it.
除非我们有证据
So unless we get some evidence,
要不他就可以拒绝
He's getting away with this.
斯嘉丽
Scarlett?
你受伤了
You're hurt.
我不知道还能去哪里
I didn't know where else to go.
过来  坐这里
Come. Sit down.
你该去医院看看
You should go to a hospital.
只是一点擦伤  我没事
It's just a few bruises. I'll be fine.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
出版公司的一个客户
A client in the publishing business
把你的地址告诉了我
Gave me your address.
自己吃晚餐吗
Dinner for one?
是的  家人都去了剧院
Yeah, my family is at the theater.
真好
Good.
我真的不想让别人看到我这个样子
I wouldn't want anyone else to see me like this.
是诺克斯干的吗
Did Knox do this to you?
-已经无所谓了  -当然有所谓
- It doesn't matter. - Of course it does.
你真的以为保护了他
Do you think that by protecting him,
就能救你自己吗  不可能
You're saving yourself somehow? Because you're not.
如果现在你不逃离他的魔爪
And if you don't get out from under his thumb now,
就再也摆脱不了了
You never will.
为什么对我这么好
Why are you so nice to me?
你怎么知道我不是
How do you know I'm not this nice
对在家门口的美女都很好呢
To all the beautiful women I find on my doorstep?
你真的觉得我漂亮吗
You really think I'm beautiful?
也许我们该
Look, maybe we should--
-对不起  -没关系
- I'm sorry. - No.
-我不该这么做  -没关系
- I shouldn't have done that. - It's okay. It's...
你受伤而且受了惊吓
You're hurt and you're scared.
但和我一起你不用那样
But you don't have to be that person with me.
你在这里很安全
You're safe here.
诺克斯杀了巴克利
Knox killed Buckley.
不  他有不在场证明
No. No, he has an alibi.
是那个牧师
The reverend?
诺克斯要我拿着这个
Knox made me take it.
丹尼尔牧师也是客人
Reverend Daniel is a client.
诺克斯这件事强迫他说谎
Knox is blackmailing him into saying
说巴克利被杀时他们在一起
They were together when Buckley was killed.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在我带你去医院  不许推辞
Now I'm taking you to a hospital. No arguments.
我在想是不是诺克斯杀了巴克利
Hey. I'm thinking Knox killed Buckley.
诺克斯有不在场证明
Knox has an alibi.
真的吗
Hmm, does he?
牧师本人提供了证明  亲自亲身
Reverend alibi in the flesh-- lots of flesh...
以及亲力亲为
Too much flesh.
-哪来的  -斯嘉丽·普莱斯给的
- Where'd you get this? - Scarlett Price.
你单独跟她见面
You saw her without me?
是啊
Uh, well, yes.
她和我们正调查的案子有关
She's a person of interest in our investigation,
-一宗谋杀案  -是  我知道
- Our murder investigation. - No, I know.
-你们在哪里见面  -在...我家
- Where'd you see her? - Uh... My apartment.
-什么  -昨晚我到家  她就在我家门口
- What? - When I came home last night, she was in my hall,
而且有人把她打伤了
And somebody had beaten her up.
你怎么不告诉我
And you didn't meat to call me?
我带她去了医院
Well, I took her to the hospital.
后来天色渐亮  我就来这里了
The night kinda got away from me, and then I came here,
你知道  为了给你惊喜
You know, to surprise you like--like I do.
这件事跟你没完
We are not done talking about this.
埃斯波西托  立刻监视诺克斯
Esposito. Have surveillance pull in Knox.
-马上办  -你对诺克斯进行监视
- On it. - Whoa. You had Knox under surveillance.
不跟我说一声
And you didn't tell me?
至少我没跟他约会
At least I didn't date with him.
-我也没约会  -真的吗
- It wasn't a date. - Really?
麻烦了  诺克斯不在家
Trouble. Knox's apartment is empty.
他肯定是趁天黑溜走了
He must have slipped out during the night.
斯嘉丽
Scarlett...
我把她送到了圣文森特医院
I left her at St. Vincent's hospital.
你好  昨晚我送一位女士到贵医院
Yes. Hello. I dropped a young woman off there last night.
叫斯嘉丽·普莱斯  被人打伤
Her name is Scarlett Price. She'd been beaten up.
我现在得跟她说话  什么  什么时候
I need to speak to her right away, please. What? When?
谢谢
Thank you.
-我刚走她就被人带走了  -是诺克斯
- A man checked her out right after I left. - Knox.
叫一队人去斯嘉丽家
Get a unit out to Scarlett's apartment
对他们俩发出通缉令
And get an A.P.B. out on both of them.
-你好  -他抓了我
- Hello. -He's got me.
斯嘉丽  别挂  别挂
Scarlett, hang on, hang on.
我想他要杀我
I think he's gonna kill me.
-你在哪里  -不知道
- Where are you? - I don't know.
-你在干什么  -斯嘉丽
- Hey, what are you doing in there?! - Scarlett.
怎么办  我们得做点什么
What do we do? We have to do something?
莱恩  打给电信公司
Ryan, get the carrier on the phone.
告诉他们  我马上能拿到
Let 'em know that I'm about a minute away
手机信号追踪令
From getting a trace warrant on the following number--
-212-555-0179   -记下了
- 212-555-0179. - Got it.
凯特·贝克特探长  警号4-1-3-1-9
This is detective Kate Beckett, badge number 4-1-3-1-9.
我要立刻跟比奥法官通话
I need to talk to judge Beall right away.
追踪到斯嘉丽的手机在
Scarlett's phone traced to the east side
东区的一栋建筑物
Of the building.
酒店经理说一个像诺克斯的人
Hotel manager said that a guy matching Knox's description
今早入住了四楼房间
Checked into room 4-F this morning.
卡塞尔  你不能进去
Castle, you're staying here.
不行  我要进去
No, I'm not.
好吧  但是跟在我后面
Okay, but stay behind me.
住手  不要
Stop! No!
警察
Police!
在那里  是诺克斯
Over there. It's Knox.
斯嘉丽
Scarlett.
没事了
Hey, it's okay.
我杀了他
I killed him.
没事了  你没事了
It's okay. You're okay.
我杀了诺克斯
I killed Knox.
他听到外面有动静  然后
He heard a noise outside, and wh--
他转身去看  我抢了他的枪
And when he turned to look, I grabbed his gun.
他叫我把枪给他  他追我
He told me to give it back. He came after me.
我叫他不要过来  但是他不听
I told him to stop, but he wouldn't.
他为什么不听
Why wouldn't he stop?
你觉得她会没事吧
You think she'll be okay?
看情况
Well, given the circumstances,
我觉得检察官不会提出指控
I don't think the D.A. will press charges.
不是  我问  她会没事吧
No, I mean, do you think she'll be okay?
不知道
I don't know.
通常女孩去卖淫
Girls in the sex industry
是由于儿时有情感障碍
Usually come from a history of childhood dysfunction.
这是很难摆脱的
It's hard to escape that.
但是有可能  对吧
But it's possible, right?
有可能
Yeah.
待好别动
Hold it right there!
卡塞尔  帮帮忙
Castle, little help?
朱利安  没事  我认识他
Oh, yeah. Julian, it's fine. He's with me.
你神经过敏吧  老兄
You are outta control, man.
好消息  我终于找到家锁匠学校
I got good news. I finally found a locksmith school
-他们愿意收我  -真的
- That's willing to admit me. - Really?
没错  只需要出具一份
Yeah. All I need is a letter of
来自警局的推荐信
Recommendation from police
-所以我来了  能帮我写吗  -不行
And I am in. Will you write it for me? - No!
-不是吧  -求你了  发发善心吧
- What? - Come on. Have a heart.
他是罪犯  如果我帮他写信
He's a criminal. If I write him a letter,
就要对他负责  我又不能
I'll be responsible for him. I cannot watch you
-一天24小时盯着你  -等等  你说什么
- 24 hours a day. - Wait a minute. What'd you say?
我要对他负责
I would be responsible for him.
不  不是  你不能一天24小时...
No, no, no. You can't watch him...
你什么时候开始监视诺克斯
When did you put the surveillance car on Knox?
就在我们离开酒吧之后
Right after we left the bar.
后来他们盯了他一整晚
And they followed them all night.
-他凌晨两点回家  -那他如何打伤斯嘉丽
-He got home on 2 a.m. - Then how could he have beaten up Scarlett?
知不知道
You guys do know that the deadbolt
你们踹门的时候
Wasn't set on this lock when you
-插销根本没插进锁里  -什么
- Guys kicked it in, right? - What?
看吧  如果我说的不对
See? If it would've been,
这整个地方都该坏了
This whole frame would've been destroyed.
锁上门  这是绑架人质的常识
Locking the door-- that's hostage taking 101.
除非斯嘉丽不是人质
Unless Scarlett wasn't a hostage.
从一开始  她就在计划这一切
She was in on it from the start.
巴克利让她在办公室工作
Buckley didn't set her up in his office
并非出于善心
And he's out of the goodness of his heart.
他需要人替他招揽生意
He needed somebody working there to man the call girl business.
没有意识到  他给了斯嘉丽机会
Not realizing that he was giving Scarlett
了解这个公司的一切
Full access to every facet of his organization.
不是诺克斯偷了客户名单
Knox didn't steal the client list?
是斯嘉丽给他的  这样他们才能
Scarlett gave it to him so that the two of them
一起打理生意
Could go into business together.
巴克利却不愿意放手  诺克斯杀之后快
And when Buckley wouldn't walk away, Knox just kill him.
没想到我们会发现应召女郎的事
Never thinking we'd find out about the call girl ring.
而当我们发现之后  斯嘉丽想到
And then when we did, Scarlett realized
救自己的唯一方法是牺牲诺克斯
That the only way to save herself was by giving up Knox
玩场最终受害者游戏  让你以为诺克斯
By playing the ultimate victim, making you believe that Knox
打伤了她  让我们以为她是自卫杀人
Beat her up so we'd think she killed him out of self-defense.
-我就是这样想的  -我们都是
- And I felt for it. - We all did.
我没有
I didn't
你好  怎样能让你今天高兴
Hi. How can I make you happy today?
有  糖果肯定有
Yes, candy is absolutely available.
你想要什么样的
How would you like her to look?
隔壁的女孩很不错
Girl next door sounds perfect.
能再确认一遍你的客户密码吗
Can you confirm your client code?
你的个人信息一致吗
And your card information is the same?
很好  七点糖果跟你见面
Great, candy will see you at 7:00.
你好  怎样能让你今天高兴
Hi. How can I make you happy today?
我要找个女孩
Yes, I'm looking for a girl.
那你完全找对人了
Well, you've certainly come to the right place.
说说你想要什么样的
Can you describe her?
她开着一辆蓝色破甲壳虫来到纽约
She came to New York in an ancient blue beetle,
底板已锈迹斑斑  中间几乎凹陷了
The floor so rusted, it literally sagged in the middle.
卡塞尔  你怎么有这个号码
Castle. How did you get this number?
有个出版商朋友
I have a friend in the publishing business.
如果让你失望了  我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I disappointed you.
我只是要找工作
I-I just needed to take a few more jobs
为了生计
To set myself up.
你从没停止过利用我  对吗  斯嘉丽
You never stop manipulating, do you, Scarlett?
我本该很讶异  真的
I should be impressed, really,
你是多么轻易地玩弄我
How easily you played me,
而我却只觉得伤心
But all I can think about is how sad it is...
美貌和智慧配一颗腐朽的心灵  真浪费
All that brains and beauty wasted on a heart gone rotten.
你处心积虑防范别人
You're so busy building up walls to keep people out,
却不知道自己被困了
You don't even realize that you're the one trapped inside...
孤独一人
All alone.
请站起来
Will you stand up, please?
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的都可能成为...
Anything you say can and will be used against you...
谢谢
Thanks.
为什么
For what?
因为你没说  我说过了
For not saying I told you so.
明天才开始说
Oh, that starts tomorrow.
为什么抱我
Oh! What was that for?
为了最好的老爸
For being the best dad ever.
确实是  还有好多理由能说明这点
It's true, you know. I have the novelty mug to prove it.
谢谢你相信我
Mm. Thanks for trusting me,
知道我有秘密  却没有逼我
For not pushing when you knew I was working something out.
我知道  你准备好了就会告诉我
Well... I knew when you were ready, you would tell me.
事情是这样的
So here it is...
学校有一项交换生计划
My school is starting a foreign exchange program
去法国的
To France.
-法国  -没错
- France? - Yeah.
-你不是被学校开除了  -没有
- You weren't kicked out of school? - No.
交换生要去三周
No, the program lasts three weeks,
所以没法陪你过生日  而且听说贝克特
And so I'd miss your birthday. And I knew that Beckett
大学时出国学习过一学期
Had spent a semester abroad in college,
我想问她这种经历
And I wanted to ask her if the experience
-值不值得  -她怎么回答的
- Was worth it. - And what'd she say?.
她说  还有几年我就得离家
She said that I'd be going off
去念大学
To college in a couple of years.
然后一切就会改变了
And that everything was gonna change,
也许现在就尝试改变是件好事
And maybe it'd be good if we got a taste of that change now.
这样啊
Well...
她很有智慧
She's a smart woman.
的确是
Yeah, she is.
但是我决定不走了
But I decided not to go anyway.
因为两年很快就会过去
Because two years will be here soon enough,
而且我已经准备好了礼物
And I already got you your present,
我想看你打开
And I want to watch you open it.
我们要用冰激凌庆祝一下
Mm. I say we celebrate with ice cream.
-不庆祝太傻了  -做我的服务员
- We'd be fools not to. - Serve me.
巧克力的还是香草味的
Chocolate or vanilla?
巧克力味
Duh. Chocolate.
可以边吃边讨论下大学
Oh, and while we're eating, we can talk about colleges.
我从升学指导办公室
I picked up a couple of brochures
拿了些宣传册
At the guidance office,
-知道哪所学校最棒吗  -哪所
- And you know what looks really cool? - What?
牛津
Oxford.
Oxford?
你知道  牛津可是在英国啊
You know--you know that's in England, right?